Guide to the George F. Kunz Papers 1862-1932 MS 358
New-York Historical Society
- Dala'l, Virchand Premchand, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Dalton, Annie Charlotte, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Dalton, Mary Louise (Missouri Historical Society), 1904 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Dalzell, Frederick B. (Hudson-Fulton Celebration Commission), 1909 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Dana, C.A. (The Sun), 1893 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Dana, Edward S. (American Journal of Science), 1885-1929 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Dana, John Cotton (Newark, NJ, Public Library), 1919 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Dana, Paul (The Sun), 1891 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Darbyshire, Leonard, 1899 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Darlington, James H. (Diocese of Harrisburg), 1919-1921 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Davis, Gherardi, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Davis, Harriet L., undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Davis, James J., 1929 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Requests a contribution to the Mooseheart school in Illinois; includes an aerial photograph of the school and campus.
- Davis, W.M., 1912 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Two letters concerning plans for a Transcontinental Excursion under the aegis of the American Geographical Society of New York.
- Dawe, Grosvenor (Society of American Authors), 1903 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Dawson, Edward M. (U.S. Government Board, Louisiana Purchase Exposition), 1904 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Dean, Bashford, 1904-1912 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Deavan, A., 1929 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- de Beel, Francis W., 1929 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Archeological Dig at Alexander Bay Area of Namaqualand
- DeForest, Robert W., 1916-1924 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- DeForest, Henry W., 1925 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- DeGraff, James W., 1925 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- de Kay, Charles, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Delafield, Joseph L., 1904-1914 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Dellenbaugh, F.S., 1928 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Demarest, H., 1915 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Demarest, W. (Rutgers College), 1918 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Dennis, L.M. (Cornell U, Department of Chemistry), 1927 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Denny, Jr., George V. (The Town Crier), 1932 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Detmer, Julian Francis, 1925 - 1926 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Deudy, F. (Encyclopedia Britannica), 1928 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- De Vinne, Theodore L. (De Vinne Press), 1884, 1903-1906 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Dewart, William T. (The Sun), 1928-1932 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- De Witt, Marguerite E., 1925 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Dexter, James V., 1887-1893 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Dillingham, W.P., 1901 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Dix, William Frederick (New York Peace Society, Board of International Hospitality), 1912, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Dixon, Joseph K. (Rodman Wanamaker Expedition of Citizenship to the North American Indian), 1912-1914, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Dodge, Cleveland H., 1915, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Dodge, Grace H., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Dodworth, Helen M., undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Dole, Nathan Haskell (American Dictionary & Cyclopedia), 1900 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Doubleday, Francis N. (Doubleday Page & Co), 1904, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Doubleday, Russell (Doubleday Page & Co), 1917 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Douglas, James, 1902, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Douglas, Norman, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Dow, Edmund LeRoy, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Downer, Charles A. (Alliance Francaise de New York), 1922 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Doyle, Hartley J. (Keystone Publishing Co), 1930 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Drake, A.W. (Century Co), 1893-1899 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Draper, A.S. (State of New York, Education Department), 1907, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Drew, D.W. (P&P Co), undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Drinker, Henry Sturgis (Lehigh U), 1908-1920 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Drummond, I., 1906 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Duffield, Howard, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Duneka, F.A. (Harper & Brothers), 1904 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Dunlap, Charles J., 1924 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Dunlap, president of the Westchester County Historical Society, acknowledges Kunz's payment of dues. The folder also holds the Westchester County YMCA financial statement for the 9 month period June 1, 1923-February 29, 1924.
- Dunn, Harris A. (Union League), 1931 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Durden, Henry S., 1902 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Dwight, Anne & Col., undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Dyer, A.M., 1904, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Among other documents, holds Kunz's draft, on Pan-American Exposition 1901 letterhead, of a proposal for a William McKinley monument.
- Misc. D., 1903, 1915, 1928, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Earle, Raymond Bartlett (Hunter College), 1918 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Eaton, Charles Frederick, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Eaton, Elizabeth K. (Recitation Classes for Girls), 1908 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Edmunds, Catherine Torr, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Edwards, George Wharton, 1923-1928 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Edwards, Harry, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Edwards, R.F. (Prudential Insurance Co), 1921 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Egelston, G. Washington, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Egleston, Thomas, 1891-1895 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Eileis (Eilers?), Emma, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Eilers, Karl, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Ellis, F., 1886 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Ellsworth, W.W. (Century Co), 1906, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Ely, Robert E. (City History Club; Civic Forum), 1907-1908, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Erb, Frederic W. (Columbia U., Library), 1924 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Ernst, C.W. (The Beacon), 1887 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Erskine, John, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Erskine, Robert S., 1911 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Estes, J. Irving (Boston Herald), 1895 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Evans, Clara Therese (Bookplate Quarterly), 1919 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Evans, E.C. (Bank of the Metropolis), 1913 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Evans, Thomas (Grolier Club), 1902 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Fabyan, Francis W., 1931 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Fairbanks, C.M. (The Sun), 1891 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Fairchild, Helen L. (University of Rochester, Department of Geology), 1902 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Fairchild, Samuel W. (Union League), 1912 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Fagnani, Charles P. (Union Theological Seminary), 1926 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Farnham, Paulding, 1901, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Farwell, Grosvenor (Union League), 1926 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Faxon, William Bailey (Century Association), undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Fenyes, Eva S., 1902 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Ferris, Jr., Ezra F. (Rev.) (St. Mary's Church, Mohegan Lake, NY), 1922 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Ferris, Maude Schuyler, 1922-1923 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Letters appear to relate to St. Mary's Church of Mohegan Lake.
- Filch, James Monroe, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Finley, John H., 1909-1929 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  State of New York Department of Education; City College of New York; New York Times; Playground and Recreation Association of America
- Fish, Stuyvesant, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Fisher, Irving, 1912-1916, 1929, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Irving writes to Kunz as a fellow member of the Committee of One Hundred on National Health of the American Association for the Advancement of Science (1912, 1916)), and for financial support of the American Eugenics Society (1931), among other matters.
- Fletcher, Angus, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Fletcher, Isaac D., 1915 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Fletcher, Jonathan (Yale University Press), 1916 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Flint, William (Library of Parliament, South Africa), 1920 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Flower, Archibald D., 1917, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Relates to various matters memorializing Shakespeare at Stratford-Upon-Avon
- Folger, Jr., Henry Clay, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  One letter from Folger in which he says he cannot help a Dr. Wallace in his research because Folger's collection is packed away in New York and Brooklyn warehouses. He hopes for a building in the future where his "treasures can be unpacked and arranged for examination."
- Foord, John, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Foote, A.E., 1884-1890 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Foot, Katherine B., 1902-1903 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Several letters, with many references to Gardner Teall. See also the folders of Teall correspondence below.
- Forbes, Jesse F., 1917 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Fortier, Jr., Matthew L. (Fordham U), 1929-1930 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Foss, E., 1917 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  A Memorial for National Prohibition
- Franklin, Fabian (The Review), 1920 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Franklin, U.B. (North American Review), 1902 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Franklinton, John (State of New Jersey, Executive Department), 1909 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  One brief letter concerning lack of plans for signal lighting for the Hudson Fulton Celebration.
- Free, E.E. (Scientific American), 1925 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Freeman, S., 1914 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Freidus, A.S. (New York Public Library), 1921 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- French, Daniel C., undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Frey, A.R. (Astor Library), 1885 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Frickmann, Gustav J. (Committee on Distribution, Messages & Papers of the Presidents), 1899 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Friederman, Emilie, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- R. Friedlander & Sohn, 1885, 1907, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Friedrick, L., 1913, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Friman, Ellen, 1902 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Frinberg, Harry (Durland Club), 1915 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Froelick, Louis D. ("Asia"), 1925 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Fuller, Harold de Wolf ("New York"), undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Fuller, William (Union League), 1904 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Fullerton, George S., 1914 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Funk, Isaac, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Furness, Caroline E. (Vassar College, Department of Astronomy), 1925 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Gager, C. Stuart (National Institute of Social Sciences), 1932 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Gallagher, C. (The Gift Shop), undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Garland, Hamlin (Town Hall Club), 1925 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Garland, J.A., 1895, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Garrett [Garnett?], Mary B.P., 1902 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Gates, Milo H. (Trinity Parish, Chapel of the Intercession), 1908, 1921-1930 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Gavin, John H. (The World), undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
- George, Edwin Stanton, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- George, Frank, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Gesner, Ida (Hudson Observer), 1913 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Gilbert, Cass, 1924, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  One letter from Gilbert and one document (unsigned draft from Kunz?) concerning the finances of a club, possibly the Century Association. One letter from Gilbert declining, as a Century Association officer, to second W. Gedney Beatty's nomination to membership. One letter from Gilbert acknowledging congratulations from Kunz on Gilbert's receiving a doctorate from Columbia.
- Gilder, Jeannette L. (The Critic and Literary World), 1905 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Gilder, R.W. (The Century magazine), 1900, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Gildersleeve, Virginia C. (Barnard College), 1929 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Gilliss, Walter (Doubleday Page & Co), 1910-1924 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Gilman, Daniel C. (Carnegie Institution of Washington), 1903 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Glassford, John (Cooper Union Alumni Association), 1917 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Goetze, Frederick A. (Columbia U), 1906 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Goldsmith, Peter H. (American Association for International Conciliation), 1916 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Gordon, Samuel G. (American Mineralogist), 1918 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Gotteril, Richard (Columbia College), 1893 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Gould, Charles W., 1916-1918 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Gould, E.R.L. (Church Club), 1915 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Gould, Florence, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Concerns, in substantial part, the Central Park Shakespeare Garden Committee, of which Kunz is Honorary President and Gould (Mrs. G. Glen Gould) is Vice-President and Secretary.
- Gould, S.C. ("Notes and Queries"), 1892 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Grace, Joseph Peter, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Granniss, Ruth Shepard (Grolier Club Library), 1906-1924 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Grant, G. (Century Association), 1904 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Grant, Percy, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Grant, U.S. (Northwestern U), 1921 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Grasty, Charles H. (New York Times), 1919 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Graves, Frank Pierrepont, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Two letters concerning Kunz's appointment as representative of the American Scenic and Historic Preservation Society to the Executive Committee named in connection with the New York State Board of Regents' plans for the 150th anniversary of the American Revolution.
- Graves, H.S. (Yale U), 1922 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Graves, Ralph H. (New York Times), 1913, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Gray, Annie E. (Women's Peace Society), 1931 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Greene, Belle da Costa (Pierpont Morgan Library), 1908-1930, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Greene, Edward L., 1909 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Greenough, John, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Greer, David H., 1915 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Gregory, Henry E., undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Gregory, Jackson, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Griffith, Mrs. D.P. (Mary E.) (Woman's Literary Work of New Jersey for Columbian Exposition), circa 1899 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Griffiths, Caroline H. (Mrs. John Lewis Griffiths) (Book Committee, Art War Relief), 1919 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Grinnell, George Bird, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Grossman, Bernard A. (American Times), 1921 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Grossman, Moses H. (Arbitration Society of America), 1924 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Grosvenor, Gilbert H., 1903, 1914, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  The 1903 letter is an invitation for Kunz to speak before the National Geographic Society on his experiments with radium, which Kunz does on November 3.
- Grover, Fredrick O. (Oberlin College, Department of Botany), 1909 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Misc. G, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Hackett, James K., 1921 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  One letter to the Shakespeare Society via Kunz in which Hackett discusses the positive response to his opening at the Odeon Theatre in Paris.
- Haldane, Mary H. (Putnam County Historical Society), 1924 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Hall, Edward Hagaman (American Scenic and Historic Preservation Society), 1899-1907 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Hall, Henry W. (The World), 1915 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Hall, James P. (New York Tribune), 1903-1905 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Hall, W.H. (Rockwood Hall Country Club, Winter Sports Committee), 1925 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Hallock, William (Columbia College), 1895 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Halsey, Francis W. (D. Appleton & Co), 1903 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Hamilton, A., undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Hamlin, Aug. C., undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Hammond, John Hays, 1907, 1925-1930 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Hampden, Walter, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Handforth, Walter S., 1908 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Harding, Edward, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Hardy, Arthur Sherburne (Cosmopolitan Magazine), 1894 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Harper, William, 1909 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Extensive comments by Harper regarding his support and proposal for an American Exposition in Berlin in 1910 (Kunz is Chairman of the American Advisory Committee for the event).
- Harris, Frank S., 1915 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Hart, Charles Henry, 1907 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Haskell, William H. (Rev.), 1903 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Haskins, Caryl Davis, 1901-1902 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Hatch, Frank C., 1920 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Hawkes, McDougall (Museum of French Art, French Institute in the United States), 1912-1915 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Hawkins, William W. (United Press Associations), 1922 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Hawn, Henry Gaines, 1916-1921 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Principally includes testimonials about Hahn's lectures on "The Soul of Things" in connection with his proposal to give the talk to some of Kunz's organizations.
- Hayes, Patrick (Cardinal), 1924, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Hegeman, Adrian G. (Union League), 1918 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Hendrick, Ellwood (Century Association), 1924 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Henry, Philip W., 1918 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Hepburn, A. Barton (History Club of New York), 1915-1920 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Herman, Grace, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Heron-Allen, Edouard, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Herring, Hubert C. (Committee on Cultural Relations with Latin America), 1931 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Hewitt, Eleanor Garnier, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Hewitt, Varal Cooper, 1908, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Heydt, George F., 1916-1932 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Includes an image of George Kunz
- Heyworth, Emerson O. (Men's Club of St. Paul's Church), 1913 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Hibben, John G. (Princeton U), 1920, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Higgins, Frank C. (American Numismatic Association), 1909 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Hildebrand, William A., 1924 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Sends Kunz a Jenny Lind-related item for the New-York Historical Society.
- Hill, Edwin C., 1917 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Hill, Elsie (City History Club of New York), 1909, 1922 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Hill, John Wesley (International Peace Forum), 1913 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Hill, Robert T. and Justina Robinson Hill, 1903, 1909 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Hill, Ruth (Richard G. Badger Publisher), 1930 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Hinton, John H. (American Folklore Society), 1902 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Hitchcock, Frank H. (Rockwood Hall Country Club), 1925-1926 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Hitchcock, Mary E., 1901, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Includes, among other documents, a list of lectures to be given by Hitchcock in 1901.
- Hitchcock, R., 1882 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Hitchcock, Ripley (D. Appleton & Co), undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Hobbs, William Herbert (Century Association), 1930 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Hodge, F.W. (American Anthropologist), 1906 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Hoffman, William Wickham, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Holden, E.G. (Grolier Club), 1894 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Holder, Charles Frederick (Californian Illustrated Magazine), 1891 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Hollis, Austin N., 1905 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Holloway, Edward S. (J.B. Lippincott Co.), 1915-1916, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Holloway, Emory (Authors Club, Walt Whitman Memorial Committee), 1925-1926 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Holls, Frederick William, 1903 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Holmes, W., 1893 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Holt, Hamilton (The Independent), 1912-1916, 1931-1932 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Holt, Mary B., undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Horwood, H.A. (Doubleday Page & Co), 1917 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Houston, Herbert S. (Doubleday Page & Co), 1910 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Hovey, E.O., 1904 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Hoving, Helga, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Howland, William B., 1901 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Hubbard, Elbert and Elbert Hubbard II (The Roycrofters), 1908-1919 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Hubbard, Gardiner G., undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Hubbard, Henry G., undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  The document appears to be Kunz's introductory remarks about Hubbard, written for someone else to present in Kunz's absence.
- Huebsch, Mrs. Daniel H., undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Hughes, Thomas (William Wesley & Son), 1888 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Humphrey, Wolcott J., 1925 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Humphreys, Alex C. (Stevens Institute of Technology), 1925 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Humphreys, Mrs. M.G. (City History Club), 1912 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Huntington, Archer M., 1913-1922 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Huntington, Henry E., 1918 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Huntington, Oliver, 1893-1901 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Huse, H.P., undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Hussey, Mary (Mount Holyoke College, Department of Biblical Literature), 1920 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Hutton, S. Janney (General Theological Seminary), 1923-1924 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Hutchins, L.W. (American Institute), 1928 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Hylan, John F., 1926 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Hyslop (Hyslof?), James H., 1915 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Misc. H, 1886, 1904, 1923 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Iddings, Joseph P., 1917 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Ihlseng, Axel O. & Olga (New York City Shakespeare Tercentenary Celebration), 1916-1918 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Iles, George (Authors Club), 1918 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Ingalls, Walter Renton (Engineering and Mining Journal), 1908-1909 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Ingersoll, E.P., undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Ingersoll, Ernest (Authors Club), 1894, 1916-1920 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Ingersoll, Mary, 1901, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Ives, Ray, 1903 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Ivins, Laura A., 1908 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  8 page letter in which Ivins recapitulates her career to date (6 years of experience) as a newspaper reporter for the Jersey City (NJ) Evening Journal in connection with asking Kunz for job leads.
- Jaccaci, August F., undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Jackson, A.V. Williams (Columbia U, American Oriental Society), 1912 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Provides Kunz with information about early historical references to elephants.
- Jacobi, Harold (Century Association), 1910 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- James I, Patriarch of Windsor, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- James, Arthur Curtiss (Mayor's Committee for the Entertainment of the U.S. Atlantic Fleet), 1915 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- James, Edward J. (University of Illinois), 1916 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Jameson, J. Franklin (Dictionary of American Biography), 1925 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Jastrow, Jr., Morris (University of Pennsylvania), 1908 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Jeglum, C.H. (American Chemical Society), 1928 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Jenks, Judor(?) (St. Nicholas press), 1895 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Jenney, William R. (St. Paul's Rectory, Hoboken, NJ), 1899-1913 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Jesup, Morris K., 1903 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Johnson, Allen (Dictionary of American Biography), 1926 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1987-1925 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Century Magazine; American Academy of Arts and Letters; New York University Hall of Fame
- Johnson, Rossiter (Authors Club), 1919-1924 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Johnson, Douglas Wilson, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Johnston, H.P. (College of the City of New York), 1909 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Johnston, Isabel M. (Mrs. John Parry), 1902 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Johnston, William (The World), 1912-1925 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Jones, E. Alfred, 1906-1909, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Jones, Henriette Ord (New York Bird and Tree Club), 1920 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Jones, John Carleton (and other signers) (University Travel Association), 1928 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Jordan, [first name?] S., undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Jordan, L.C. Levin (Cooper Union), 1916 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Joyce, C.M., 1909 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Juen, Emile C. (Museum of French Art, French Institute in the United States), 1915 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Misc. J, 1892, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Kahn, Albert, 1925 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Kaldenberg, F.R., 1916 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Keeler, Annie, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Keene, John Harington, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Keller, Helen, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Typed letter, signed. Appeal for financial support for the American Foundation for the Blind.
- Keller, William (New York Times), 1917 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Kelley, J.D. Jerrold (New York Herald), 1915 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Kelley, Frank Bergen (City History Club of New York), 1922 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Kelly, N., 1930 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Kemp, James F. (Columbia U), 1899, 1908-1925 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Kennedy, John B. (Collier's), 1930 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Invitation to speak on the Collier's Hour radio broadcast.
- Kent, H.W. (Grolier Club), 1903-1904, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Kern, Albert J.H., 1907 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Kerr, Helen C. (Woman's League for the Protection of Riverside Park), 1924 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Kimball, L.L., 1906 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Kingsley, Darwin P., 1916-1929 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Kirby, Gustavus T. (American Olympic Committee), 1920 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  American Olympic Committee, Seventh Olympiad, Antwerp, Belgium, 1920 letterhead. Thank you for contribution.
- Kirby, Thomas E. (American Art Association), 1912 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Klebs, Arnold C. (Grolier Club), 1918 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Knecht, Marcel (Le Matin, Paris), 1928-1932 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Knight, Annie H., undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Knight, Charles P(or R?)., 1926 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Knowles, Horace G., 1920 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Speech by Mr. Tejada suggesting that U.S. loan money to Europe through Latin America.
- Kramer, Ella, 1909 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Kraus, Edward H. (University of Michigan), 1918-1925 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Kyle, Howard, 1916-1917 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Misc. K, 1903, 1916, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Grolier Club; University of California
- Ladd, A.C. (Cosmopolitan Magazine), 1893 (Box 3, Folder 11)